<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HCD on ckm</title>
    <link>https://chase-mortensen.github.io/tags/hcd/</link>
    <description>Recent content in HCD on ckm</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:12:29 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://chase-mortensen.github.io/tags/hcd/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Gaming Device</title>
      <link>https://chase-mortensen.github.io/projects/mobile-gaming/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:12:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chase-mortensen.github.io/projects/mobile-gaming/</guid>
      <description>Intro In 2016, I took a class called Digital Making and Learning that ultimately lead me to the Learn Explore Design Lab . This class was amazing and was where I first read Don Norman&amp;rsquo;s The Design of Everyday Things . I learned about feedback, signifiers, and many other aspects of human-centered design.
For my final project in the course, I wanted to make a mobile gaming device. I loved my Game Boy Advance when I was younger and wanted to recreate the experience I had with my own modern version.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Task List</title>
      <link>https://chase-mortensen.github.io/projects/task-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 02:23:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chase-mortensen.github.io/projects/task-list/</guid>
      <description>Current Project This project (code here ) began as a simple to-do app. The user can add, edit, delete, and mark tasks as complete, as well as filter the list by pending, complete, or all tasks. It isn&amp;rsquo;t fully functional, but you can see a demo here . This project was built in Vue.js and is currently styled using vuetify. It is currently hosted using Firebase.
  Current Version ↑   What Next?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FaceOverlay</title>
      <link>https://chase-mortensen.github.io/projects/faceoverlay/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 20:23:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chase-mortensen.github.io/projects/faceoverlay/</guid>
      <description>Intro FaceOverlay (also known as SmileyCluster ) is an educational tool for machine learning under development in Dr. Zhen Bai&amp;rsquo;s lab at the University of Rochester. I was able to work on the project through an NSF-funded internship over the summer of 2019. Dr. Bai and her lab were amazing to work with and I learned a lot about iterative design and experiment design through that experience.
  UR&amp;rsquo;s Rush Rhees Library ↑   Chernoff Faces Chernoff Faces are a tool for visualizing multivariate data.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>