<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ckm</title>
    <link>https://chase-mortensen.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on ckm</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chase-mortensen.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Tower: Git for Humans</title>
      <link>https://chase-mortensen.github.io/posts/git-tower/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chase-mortensen.github.io/posts/git-tower/</guid>
      <description>Your browser does not support the video tag.  I didn&amp;rsquo;t start programming until college. When I first started, it was a lot to take in. The number of languages and technologies seemed innumerable (I think it feels even more so that way now).
Arguably, one of the most confusing technologies to learn was Git, which is a version control tool. It&amp;rsquo;s really an amazing tool - it allows users to track changes in files and collaborate with other users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Vitals 101: The Foundation of Good User Experience</title>
      <link>https://chase-mortensen.github.io/posts/web-vitals/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 20:54:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chase-mortensen.github.io/posts/web-vitals/</guid>
      <description>This post is an introduction to the Web Vitals initiative from Google and why Web Vitals matter for your sites. Most of the content is summarized from Google’s articles on Web Vitals [1] and there are links throughout this article for further reading.
Part 1: What are Web Vitals and why do they matter? Your browser does not support the video tag.  Web Vitals are site metrics that measure some critical pillars of user experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Task List</title>
      <link>https://chase-mortensen.github.io/projects/task-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 02:23:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chase-mortensen.github.io/projects/task-list/</guid>
      <description>Current Project This project (code here) began as a simple to-do app. The user can add, edit, delete, and mark tasks as complete, as well as filter the list by pending, complete, or all tasks. It isn&amp;rsquo;t fully functional, but you can see a demo here. This project was built in Vue.js and is currently styled using vuetify. It is currently hosted using Firebase.
 Current Version ↑   What Next?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Gaming Device</title>
      <link>https://chase-mortensen.github.io/projects/mobile-gaming/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:12:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chase-mortensen.github.io/projects/mobile-gaming/</guid>
      <description>Intro In 2016, I took a class called Digital Making and Learning that ultimately lead me to the Learn Explore Design Lab. This class was amazing and was where I first read Don Norman&amp;rsquo;s The Design of Everyday Things. I learned about feedback, signifiers, and many other aspects of human-centered design.
For my final project in the course, I wanted to make a mobile gaming device. I loved my Game Boy Advance when I was younger and wanted to recreate the experience I had with my own modern version.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FaceOverlay</title>
      <link>https://chase-mortensen.github.io/projects/faceoverlay/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 20:23:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chase-mortensen.github.io/projects/faceoverlay/</guid>
      <description>Intro FaceOverlay (also known as SmileyCluster) is an educational tool for machine learning under development in Dr. Zhen Bai&amp;rsquo;s lab at the University of Rochester. I was able to work on the project through an NSF-funded internship over the summer of 2019. Dr. Bai and her lab were amazing to work with and I learned a lot about iterative design and experiment design through that experience.
 UR&amp;rsquo;s Rush Rhees Library ↑   Chernoff Faces Chernoff Faces are a tool for visualizing multivariate data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://chase-mortensen.github.io/about/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chase-mortensen.github.io/about/about-me/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Chase.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a few quick facts about me:
 I&amp;rsquo;m a husband (as of August 2021!), musician, artist, uncle, skier, mountain biker, and avid pickleballer. I love being outside, traveling, and trying as many vegan restaurants as possible. Severance is currently my favorite show - hit me up if you want to talk about it!    I am a recent computer science graduate from USU and I value simple, usable design.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
